# Don Alfons Nisnoni Resume

### **PERSONAL DATA**



Date of Birth: 18 September 1995 (26 years old)

Address: Semangka street, Amnesi, Kota Raja sub-district, Kupang city, East Nusa Tenggara, Indonesia

Phone: +6283809705594

Preffered Position: Front-end Web Developer

Email: donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com

Website: donnisnoni.github.io

**GitHub:** donnisnoni **LinkedIn:** donnisnoni

### **SUMMARY**

# Hello!

My name is Don Alfons Nisnoni. I'm a passionate, motivated, and creative web developer with 2 years of experience. Mostly focused on front-end, but has the flexibility and experience to work on backend as well. Experienced with NodeJS, VueJS, ReactJS, PHP, and testing.

I am very enthusiastic and always eager to learn more about technology especially web development both front-end and back-end. I always look forward to building things and products with it.

## **EDUCATION**

### Diploma Degree of Computer Science @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - GPA: 3.44 - Graduated on Nov 2020 due COVID-19

### **SKILLS**

Thing's that I've touch so far:

### Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG, Discourse

#### **Databases:**

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

### Programming Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP, Python

### Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, React, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

### Technique:

Responsive Web Design, a11y, i18n, PWA

### **EXPERIENCES**

### Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

- Build a website for improve student's online services
- Upgrade & improve campus main website
- · Create work email for lecturer's
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI
- Upgrade campus tech stacks

### Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2021 - May 2021 @ Vlingo

• Implementing vlingo/auth UI

### Front-End Web Developer

May 2021 - Present @ Bali Casa Villas

- Maintain Alphien and Alphien Dashboard using VueJS and NuxtJS
- Maintain Domaine Des Meuniers and Hotel De La Poste, and website using Laravel
- Extending a discourse forum ( Alphien's Forum) (Develop discourse widgets and extensions)
- Develop JupyterLab extensions

